BRENDAN M. KANTA

3655 CLARE DOWNS PATH, ROSEMOUNT, MN 55068 (651)242-0292 EMAIL: BRENDAN.K29@GMAIL.COM

SUMMARY

Computer Science Major at the University of Wisconsin Stout. Interested in a job in the cybersecurity field. Entry level Supervisor with 5 years of experience training store associates, supervising store associates and taking care of customers. Able to quickly learn processes and teach others.

SELECTED ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Helped in the creation of an IT internship program at Rosemount High School. The program helps students troubleshoot issues with school issued technology
- Completed data structures and algorithms in Java
- Completed Intro to Cybersecurity
- Completed networking courses in CISCO
- Prior knowledge in Java, HTML, JavaScript, and C++.
- Familiar with Eclipse, VMWare, VirtualBox, and Processing.
- Elected Secretary of the University Of Wisconsin Stout Auto Club.

EDUCATION

University Of Wisconsin Stout – Menomonie Wisconsin, attended September 2019 – present anticipate Graduation date spring 2023. GPA 3.0

Inver Hills Community College- Inver Grove Minnesota, attended September 2017- May 2019

Rosemount High School- Rosemount Minnesota, attended September 2015, graduated June 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Culvers, Menomonie

Culvers Crew Trainer (10/2019 – present)

-Taught processes and procedures of the restaurant to new hires

Target, Apple Valley Mn

Target Team Member (11/2017 – 7/20)

- -Cross trained in 18+ different positions
- -Self-checkout trainer

Culvers, Rosemount Mn

Culvers Shift Leader/Supervisor (2/2016 – 11/2017)

- -Responsible for the front-end team
- -Opened and closed the restaurant
- -Attended Leadership meetings